Bar Pizza! You know the concept is nothing new but when the peeps over at good old B-dubs do it their way guys you already know
So stay tuned because up next I've got the all-new honey barbecue boneless bar pizza on tap
All right, let me pick up one of these pieces here and wow, this is very nice cut very beautifully
It's the honey barbecue boneless bar pizza here at Buffalo Wild Wings. Let's peep this out
Mmm
Sweet we're right off the break outside of the sweetness
I'm kind of getting a focaccia vibe with this one guys almost like a flatbread type of situation
I wouldn't say pizza necessarily, but again, it's not really a traditional pizza in that sense. Let's keep going in
Hot pickled peppers there it is. Oh
Little steamy
Mmm alright so do me a favor like always drop some comments down below
Let me know what you thought of this particular one
I mean have you given this one a shot over here at B-dubs already did it satisfy your
Expectations in terms of flavor and maybe the value for $9.99 drop those comments down below and definitely let me know